[{"answer": "They could.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Can anybody just say that I have the best movies?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny, all the past school massacres and you know, I read about them in the newspaper, Columbine, Aurora, you know, we shield deeply for four or five days and then we get on with our lives, you know.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Why are you doing this and why do you care so passionately?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, you know, first of all, all the people that are pro guns are mad at me.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What more can you tell me about the movie and Meryl Streep's involvement?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Are you nervous about taking on the NRA?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "No, because I've seen now what happens.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "But does that worry you?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I don't think that, you know, I think -- I don't think you see a movie like \"Lone Survivor\", Peter Berg's movie.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you want to make any more movies glamorizing guns?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I mean, I would imagine that there's got to be some way of judging someone's mental capacity before they have a gun, you know, in Connecticut, it doesn't need to have a gun.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think that is a fair thing for people to stand behind that they have this constitutional right?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Because he hasn't found.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Why is that and what is he got to do?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Morgan and Meryl.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "You and Meryl?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Don't ask me for first billing.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "It's got a certain ring to it isn't it?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "It just -- and look at the box office.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What does that tell us Harvey?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "You have a hard life, don't you?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I can't.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "You want to live with your father?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "No, Randy.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Ma, is it him?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: We're going to have to use your real name, Philomena.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "That's a lovely -- or somebody have that?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "When I started out, the only thing I started out was to find Anthony and to tell my story as it was -- as it happened completely having true story.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What is your view about that allegation really that it makes the Catholic Church look bad deliberately?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I couldn't believe it.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "How did that make you feel when you discovered that?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, at that time I was only a young teenager.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Do you believe that is what happened?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well Brent Bozell, Philomena was the one and mean a conservative columnist to, you know, accuse me of that.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I don't ...", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "You based it to everybody haven't -- don't you?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I'm 100 percent.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Are you taking Philomena to the Oscars?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Oh I have to be -- I going to ...", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How are you going to feel about that Philomena?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": ", PAID $350,000 TO HUNT AND KILL RARE BLACK RHINO: Well, I justified the name conservation, I justified in belief system and sustainable use.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How do you justify what you have done?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "This is what is all about.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "John Jackson, you're supportive of Corey Knowlton, why?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Hunters have a very special relationship with animals they pursue.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Why do you -- why do people need to do that and why would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Are you comfortable with that?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "This is a case of critically endangered species being hunted for trophy.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Jeff Flocken, in terms of the validity of a hunter's right to hunt the black rhino particularly the elderly black rhino's who have no longer have breeding use and who would perhaps be killed anyway -- certainly it seems to be the suggestion that's not been disputed -- what is actually wrong in having it hunted in this particular way compared to any other way?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there are scientists who can clearly dispute the need to kill endangered animal.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "But let me pick you up, Jeff Flocken, on that point if you remove the hunting this of the photographic memory stuff that goes on with social media and distinct to the actual killing of this black rhino which would probably be killed anyway, what is the sensible argument against it?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "He is not the expert.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "John Jackson, he's not buying it why is he wrong?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I will if he survives the encounter I'll congratulate him for knowing a rhino was only a hunter can do.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Will you pose for the picture with him when he's posing proudly by the dead rhino?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I certainly would.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "But would you pose with him for the picture if he asked you to?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "The difficult thing he has is that people think this scandal fits him and what they know of him.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Patrick, what do you make in this?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I'm a proud Jersey resident.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "And you are a New Jersey resident?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I knew that President Clinton particularly had a lot of misgivings with my dad's moving towards an endorsement for then Senator Barack Obama.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Well, that people that recover from this brain illness have a lot to give the world that more than just their sobriety.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "What is the point of the book and what is the key thing that you want me to take away from that?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Well, first off, he said war on drugs was an abysmal failure and I worked in Congress to try to move to treatment and treat these issues as health issues, not criminal justice issues.", "docId": "140117pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "In terms of the claim that people said it's the gateway to two other of the drugs, do you subscribe to that?", "qSentId": 627}]